<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE privacy SYSTEM "privacy.dtd">
<privacy>
    <section>
        <title>Privacy Policy</title>
        <content>Brayan&apos;s Cafe is committed to providing quality services to you and this policy outlines our ongoing obligations to you in respect of how we manage your Personal Information.

            We have adopted the Australian Privacy Principles (APPs) contained in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (the Privacy Act). The NPPs govern the way in which we collect, use, disclose, store, secure and dispose of your Personal Information.
            
            A copy of the Australian Privacy Principles may be obtained from the website of The Office of the Australian Information Commissioner at www.aoic.gov.au
            </content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>What is Personal Information and why do we collect it?</title>
        <content>Personal Information is information or an opinion that identifies an individual. Examples of Personal Information we collect include: names, addresses, email addresses, phone and facsimile numbers.

            This Personal Information is obtained in many ways including interviews, correspondence, by mobile phone and facsimile, by email, via our website www.koalatshirt.com.au, from your website, from media and publications, from other publicly available sources, from cookies- delete all that aren&apos;t applicable and from third parties. We don&apos;t guarantee website links or policy of authorised third parties.
            
            We collect your Personal Information for the primary purpose of providing our services to you, providing information to our clients and marketing. We may also use your Personal Information for secondary purposes closely related to the primary purpose, in circumstances where you would reasonably expect such use or disclosure. You may unsubscribe from our mailing/marketing lists at any time by contacting us in writing.
            
            
            When we collect Personal Information we will, where appropriate and where possible, explain to you why we are collecting the information and how we plan to use it.
            </content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Sensitive Information</title>
        <content>Sensitive information is defined in the Privacy Act to include information or opinion about such things as an individual's racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, membership of a political association, religious or philosophical beliefs, membership of a trade union or other professional body, criminal record or health information.

            Sensitive information will be used by us only:
            
            • For the primary purpose for which it was obtained.
            
            • For a secondary purpose that is directly related to the primary purpose
            
            • With your consent; or where required or authorised by law.
            </content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Third Parties</title>
        <content>Where reasonable and practicable to do so, we will collect your Personal Information only from you. However, in some circumstances we may be provided with information by third parties. In such a case we will take reasonable steps to ensure that you are made aware of the information provided to us by the third party.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Disclosure of Personal Information</title>
        <content>Your Personal Information may be disclosed in a number of circumstances including the following: • Third parties where you consent to the use or disclosure; and • Where required or authorised by law.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Security of Personal Information</title>
        <content>Your Personal Information is stored in a manner that reasonably protects it from misuse and loss and from unauthorized access, modification or disclosure. When your Personal Information is no longer needed for the purpose for which it was obtained, we will take reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify your Personal Information. However, most of the Personal Information is or will be stored in client files which will be kept by us for a minimum of 7 years.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Access to your Personal Information</title>
        <content>You may access the Personal Information we hold about you and to update and/or correct it, subject to certain exceptions. If you wish to access your Personal Information, please contact us in writing.

            Brayan&apos;s Cafe will not charge any fee for your access request but may charge an administrative fee for providing a copy of your Personal Information.
            
            In order to protect your Personal Information we may require identification from you before releasing the requested information.
            </content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Maintaining the Quality of your Personal Information</title>
        <content>It is an important to us that your Personal Information is up to date. We will take reasonable steps to make sure that your Personal Information is accurate, complete and up-to-date. If you find that the information we have is not up to date or is inaccurate, please advise us as soon as practicable so we can update our records and ensure we can continue to provide quality services to you.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Web Security</title>
        <content>Brayan&apos;s Cafe uses the services of companies that are experts in the management and security of personal information. These companies have storage servers inside and outside the country to ensure that your information is safe.

            To whom do we transfer your personal information? Your personal information may at some time be transferred to government entities which need to maintain a purchasing account for the payment of taxes.
            </content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Policy Updates</title>
        <content>This Policy may change from time to time and is available on our website.

            Storage: at Brayan&apos;s Cafe we use external servers which allow us to safeguard your information and in this way guarantee that said information does not fall into foreign hands which may be misused to harm any of our clients.
            </content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Privacy Policy Complaints and Enquiries</title>
        <content>If you have any queries or complaints about our Privacy Policy please contact us at:</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title></title>
        <content>451 Pitt St, Haymarket Sydney, NSW</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title></title>
        <content>jaime19854@brayanscafe.com.au</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title></title>
        <content>Mobile: 02 9262 5678</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Code Of Ethics</title>
        <content></content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>The primacy of public interest:</title>
        <content>At Brayan&apos;s Cafe, public interests are given priority over personal or company interests.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Improving the quality of life:</title>
        <content>In our company we strive to satisfy and improve the quality of life of our employees and our clients.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Hosnesty:</title>
        <content>We are characterized by being honest in providin our services and products and also demostrating our skills and knowledge.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Competition:</title>
        <content>We work with responsibility and dedication for our interested party.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Professional Development:</title>
        <content>The Brayan&apos;s Cafe enhances the professional development of staff.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Professionalism:</title>
        <content>We are focusing on respect and integrity in pur personal.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Fair Treatment</title>
        <content>Brayan&apos;s Cafe Owner and Employees must treat people with respect since in the way we want others to treat us, we cannot discriminate against anyone because of any difficulty, or physical difference or way of thinking, much less because of sexual orientation.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Privacy:</title>
        <content>It is prohibited for me or other co-workers to take personal advantage of clients personal information either to sell this information or make calls personally.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Communication:</title>
        <content>As a company we have the obligation to inform customers of any movement such as updating, maintenance that we are going to do regarding the security of the data collected by the company or any failure that we make causes loss of information.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>System Integrity:</title>
        <content>The company must ensure the proper functioning of the systems used gor the collection, storage of information and also for billing.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Co-operation:</title>
        <content>Exchange information, experiences of success and difficulties experienced at work with information colleagues so that they and I can learn and avoid future errors that harm the proper functioning of the company's processes.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Honesty:</title>
        <content>I must be transparent when reporting my capabilities and seek help from qualified personnel to carry out any activity that I do not feel adequately capable of performing.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Education:</title>
        <content>I have the duty to improve my skills day by day to provide the best service for the company and in this way guarantee the proper functioning of all systems.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Social Responsibility:</title>
        <content>I have the duty to improve and stay updated with respect to computer science and information management laws to avoid legal problems for the company and safeguard the computer rights of clients.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Workplace Quality:</title>
        <content>I will do everything in my power to provide a friendly and healthy environment for users who work in the company as far as IT is concerned.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Grievance complaints</title>
        <content>Brayan&apos;s Cafe knows that every employee has the right to file a complaint with their manager if they believe that a decision, behavior or action that affects their employment is unfair. An employee may file a complaint about any performance improvement measures taken against him or her.
            We aim to resolve problems and complaints promptly and as close to the source as possible. When necessary, Brayan&apos;s Cafe will escalate a complaint to the next higher level of authority for further discussion and resolution, and will continue to escalate it to the next higher level until resolved.
            Managers will make every effort to resolve complaints objectively, discreetly and quickly. Please note that complaints that are erroneous, vexatious and lack substance may result in disciplinary action being taken against the employee making the complaint.
            </content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Procedure</title>
        <content></content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title></title>
        <content>1. The employee should attempt to resolve the complaint as close to the source as possible. This can be informal and verbal. At this stage, every effort should be made to resolve a complaint before the formal complaints process begins. If the matter still cannot be resolved, the process continues and is formalized.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title></title>
        <content>2. To initiate the formal complaint, complainants must fully describe their complaint in writing, with dates and, where possible, locations and how they have already attempted to resolve the complaint.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title></title>
        <content>3. The persons against whom the complaint/complaint is made must be given full details of the allegations against them. They must be given the opportunity and a reasonable time to respond before the process continues.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title></title>
        <content>4. If the complaint still cannot be resolved, refer the matter to the most senior manager for consideration and final decision. A complaint brought to this level must be in writing from the employee.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title></title>
        <content>At Brayan&apos;s Cafe we have the complaints and claims department where you can express any disagreement you have so that it can be overcome in the best way and thus have the best work environment.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title></title>
        <content>2024</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title></title>
        <content>© Brayan&apos;s Cafe 2024</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title></title>
        <content>November 3, 2024</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title></title>
        <content>The content of this website, including downloadable files such as photographs, videos, audio clips, texts, logos and trademarks and even this website, are the property of Brayan&apos;s Cafe and are protected by the Copyright Law of 1968.
        </content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title></title>
        <content>It is not permitted to reproduce, transmit, publish, display, delete, modify and/or create designs based on our products for commercial purposes.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title></title>
        <content>You may download, copy and print the content of this website for personal, but non-commercial use as long as it does not violate any trademark or copyright.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title></title>
        <content>We reserve the right to cancel or block the subscription of any customer for a certain period of time if we see that they are misusing the Brayan&apos;s Cafe website.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title></title>
        <content>This policy may be updated without prior notice and the client is recommended to read it frequently.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title></title>
        <content>For more detailed information, visit www.copyright.com.au and www.copyright.org.au</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Intellectual Propertyand Security.</title>
        <content>All intellectual property developed by employees during their employment with Brayan&apos;s Cafe, including discoveries or inventions made in the performance of their duties related in any way to the business of Brayan&apos;s Cafe, will remain the property of Brayan&apos;s Cafe.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title></title>
        <content>Employees may be given access to confidential information, data, business property, keys to premises or any other business related property/information in the performance of their duties. This must be protected and used only in the interests of Brayan&apos;s Cafe.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Employees must not:</title>
        <content>• disclose or use any part of any confidential information outside of the performance of their duties and in the interests of Brayan&apos;s Cafe; or
            • authorise or be involved in the improper use or disclosure of confidential information;
            • during or after their employment without the Employer's written consent, other than as required by law.
            </content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title></title>
        <content>&apos;Confidential information&apos; includes any information in any form relating to Brayan&apos;s Cafe and related bodies, clients or businesses, which is not in the public domain.</content>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title></title>
        <content>Employees must act in good faith towards Brayan&apos;s Cafe and must prevent (or if impractical, report) the unauthorised disclosure of any confidential information.Failure to comply with this policy may result in performance improvement proceedings including dismissal, and Brayan&apos;s Cafe may also pursue monetary damages or other remedies.</content>
    </section>

    <!-- Agrega más secciones aquí según sea necesario -->
</privacy>
